

ABOUT ME

Purpose: Based on my previous work experience, I would like to deal with full stack development as CMS systems, e-commerce, PHP more profoundly, and be valuable co-worker for my colleagues. I would like to work for a company where I can go on developing professional skill and knowledge, I'm committed to my profession; therefore, I do not have any problems working on extraordinary and unusual cases. I am open for innovative solutions; I am enthusiastic and proactive in my tasks. I put a great emphasis on further education. This profession is exciting and offers a lot of opportunities for me to develop, both as a person and professionally.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+36301289844

EMAIL:

judit aczel@aol.com

LINKEDIN: Profile

JUDIT ACZÉL

WORK EXPERIENCE

Black Cell Magyarország Kft SOC L1 Analyst

02/01/2020-04/02/2021

- -Client system monitoring with (IBM Qradar, Splunk, Vectra, MCAS, O365, JIRA and some of the online investigating scanner) reporting and investigating events.
- -My main task was to develop, maintain and protect the Wordpress websites of my company in Hungarian and English / and an external company.
- -In addition, I developed a WordPress Wiki Knowledge Base for internal use.

Web: https://blackcell.hu; https://blackcell.io;

https://welovedigital.hu;

MKK Magyar Követeléskezelő Zrt Application expert

06/08/2018-13/12/2019

- -PL/SQL database programming (Data cleaning in existing databases)
- -Preparation of financial and accounting tasks and statements (PL/SQL és Power BI)
- -Assessment of the development needs of the internal system (Kökény .Net application), documentation and sending development tickets to external developers.
- -SQL and application log analysis from Kökény system
- -We used TOPDESK as a ticket system
- -My main task was to completely modernize the company's existing website, with online payment integration.

Web: https://mkkzrt.hu

KMPG Global Services Hungary_ SharePoint analyst

02/01/2017 - 01/08/2018

- -SharePoint collab site programming, site groups and user's management with permissions settings
- -SharePoint, SharePoint Designer and C # development tasks
- -MS SQL and SSRS report generation
- -ULS Viewer, Event logs, SQL database logs analysis
- -TFS ticket system
- -My main task was to migrate from SharePoint 2007 to SharePoint 2013 with collab web site with content and settings.

Delta csoport Application developer

01/06/2016 - 01/12/2016

- -SharePoint servers (2013, 2016), Windows server (2012R2), SQL servers (2012, 2014) installing and configuring, managing user groups permissions.
- -SharePoint Designer, SharePoint Branding Development Competencies and skills
- -Microsoft IIS web server, SCVMM and Hyper-V virtual environments installation and configuration knowledge
- -MS SQL, PowerShell, Caml query creation,
- -SharePoint and C# development tasks
- -Event viewer, ULS Viewer, log analysis,
- -SharePoint deployments with PowerShell and C#
- -Release preparation and installation on client systems
- -Building an auto build system with Team Foundation Server

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Szent György Media and Informatics Secondary School

Software development OKJ (54-213-05)

Training 360

CSharp programming (Microsft 20483)
Administering Windows Server 2012 (Microsoft 20411)
Installing and configuring Windows Server 2012 (Microsoft 20410)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother language: Hungarian

English

Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	Writing
B2	B2	B2	B2	B2

German

Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	Writing
A2	A2	A2	A2	A2

NETWORK AND MEMBERSHIPS

Hírközlési és Informatikai Tudományos Egyesület (HTE) https://www.hte.hu/

HTE meets monthly.

Interesting and meaningful lectures can be heard every month from cyber security and prevention. New technology solutions and other practices.

HOBBIES AND INTEREST

Hobbies

I prefer leisure activities like walking and cycling when the weather allows. In summer I always go kayaking with my mother to Lake Balaton, but in winter we used to go ice skating or hockey.

<u>Interests</u>

I am very interested in CMS systems, PHP coding, databases, UI / UX and e-commerce website, as well as development solutions. I want to get really deep into these, so I am taking some courses on online.

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

JAVA / JAVA Web programming C/C++ SVN, GIT UML JavaScript JQuery, React JS, Type Script AJAX Database programming (MS SQL, MySQL, Maria DB, PL/SQL)